<resources>
    <string name="app_name">InspiringPeople</string>
    <string name="carmackData"><b>John D. Carmack (born August 20, 1970)</b> is an American computer programmer, engineer, and businessman. He co-founded id Software. Carmack was the lead programmer of the id video games Commander Keen, Wolfenstein 3D, Doom, Quake, Rage and their sequels. Carmack is best known for his innovations in 3D graphics, such as his Carmack\'s Reverse algorithm for shadow volumes.</string>
    <string name="leeData"><b>Sir Timothy John Berners-Lee (born 8 June 1955)</b>, also known as TimBL, is an English engineer and computer scientist, best known as the inventor of the World Wide Web. He is currently a professor of Computer Science at the University of Oxford. He made a proposal for an information management system in March 1989, and he implemented the first successful communication between a Hypertext Transfer Protocol (HTTP) client and server via the internet in mid-November the same year.</string>
    <string name="katzData"><b>Phillip Walter Katz (November 3, 1962 – April 14, 2000)</b> was a computer programmer best known as the co-creator of the Zip file format for data compression, and the author of PKZIP, a program for creating zip files that ran under DOS. A copyright lawsuit between System Enhancement Associates (SEA) and Katz\'s company, PKWARE, Inc., was widely publicized in the BBS community in the late 1980s. Phil Katz\'s software business was very successful, but he struggled with social isolation and chronic alcoholism in the last years of his life.</string>
    <string name="leeQuote">The Web as I envisaged it, we have not seen it yet. The future is still so much bigger than the past.</string>
    <string name="carmackQuote">Programming is not a zero-sum game. Teaching something to a fellow programmer doesn\'t take it away from you. I\'m happy to share what I can, because I\'m in it for the love of programming.</string>
    <string name="katzQuote">It was just a hobby. I didn\'t expect it to turn into a business.</string>
</resources>
